Wake up.
HEY! LET ME GO- WHAT THE FUCK IS THIS?
Go on.
Out of everyone who has laid on this table like you,
you're one special guy, you know that?
I mean, (laughs), the things you've done
have made you more deserving to end up here - than anyone else.
I'LL FUCKING KILL YOU.
Yes..
Death is no stranger to either of us.
We both use it as our own form of.. release.
And now its time - for YOUR release.
PLEASE.. YOU'VE GOT THE WRONG PERSON
I HAVENT DONE ANYTHING - I'M INNOCENT!
Ha! Look at you go.
You can't wiggle yourself out of this like you did
with the cops a few years back.
I know what you did to them,
JAMES.
I know you strung them up like sacks of meat.
I know you dug them a few shallow graves in your shitty
little backyard.
Now, it's your turn.
Goodnight, James.